(function() {

    angular
        .module('flashCards')
        .factory('multiplicationMockData', multiplicationMockData);

    multiplicationMockData.$inject = ['cardFactory'];

    function multiplicationMockData(cardFactory) {
        return {
            cards: [
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 1", "Answer:", "1"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 2", "Answer:", "2"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 3", "Answer:", "3"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 4", "Answer:", "4"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 5", "Answer:", "5"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 6", "Answer:", "6"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 7", "Answer:", "7"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 8", "Answer:", "8"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 9", "Answer:", "9"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 10", "Answer:", "10"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 11", "Answer:", "11"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "1 X 12", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 1", "Answer:", "2"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 2", "Answer:", "4"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 3", "Answer:", "6"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 4", "Answer:", "8"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 5", "Answer:", "10"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 6", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 7", "Answer:", "14"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 8", "Answer:", "16"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 9", "Answer:", "18"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 10", "Answer:", "20"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 11", "Answer:", "22"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "2 X 12", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 1", "Answer:", "3"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 2", "Answer:", "6"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 3", "Answer:", "9"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 4", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 5", "Answer:", "15"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 6", "Answer:", "18"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 7", "Answer:", "21"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 8", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 9", "Answer:", "27"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 10", "Answer:", "30"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 11", "Answer:", "33"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "3 X 12", "Answer:", "36"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 1", "Answer:", "4"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 2", "Answer:", "8"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 3", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 4", "Answer:", "16"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 5", "Answer:", "20"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 6", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 7", "Answer:", "28"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 8", "Answer:", "32"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 9", "Answer:", "36"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 10", "Answer:", "40"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 11", "Answer:", "44"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "4 X 12", "Answer:", "48"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 1", "Answer:", "5"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 2", "Answer:", "10"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 3", "Answer:", "15"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 4", "Answer:", "20"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 5", "Answer:", "25"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 6", "Answer:", "30"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 7", "Answer:", "35"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 8", "Answer:", "40"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 9", "Answer:", "45"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 10", "Answer:", "50"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 11", "Answer:", "55"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "5 X 12", "Answer:", "60"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 1", "Answer:", "6"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 2", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 3", "Answer:", "18"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 4", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 5", "Answer:", "30"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 6", "Answer:", "36"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 7", "Answer:", "42"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 8", "Answer:", "48"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 9", "Answer:", "54"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 10", "Answer:", "60"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 11", "Answer:", "66"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "6 X 12", "Answer:", "72"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 1", "Answer:", "7"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 2", "Answer:", "14"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 3", "Answer:", "21"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 4", "Answer:", "28"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 5", "Answer:", "35"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 6", "Answer:", "42"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 7", "Answer:", "49"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 8", "Answer:", "56"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 9", "Answer:", "63"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 10", "Answer:", "70"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 11", "Answer:", "77"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "7 X 12", "Answer:", "84"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 1", "Answer:", "8"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 2", "Answer:", "16"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 3", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 4", "Answer:", "32"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 5", "Answer:", "40"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 6", "Answer:", "48"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 7", "Answer:", "56"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 8", "Answer:", "64"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 9", "Answer:", "72"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 10", "Answer:", "80"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 11", "Answer:", "88"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "8 X 12", "Answer:", "96"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 1", "Answer:", "9"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 2", "Answer:", "18"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 3", "Answer:", "27"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 4", "Answer:", "36"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 5", "Answer:", "45"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 6", "Answer:", "54"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 7", "Answer:", "63"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 8", "Answer:", "72"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 9", "Answer:", "81"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 10", "Answer:", "90"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 11", "Answer:", "99"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "9 X 12", "Answer:", "108"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 1", "Answer:", "10"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 2", "Answer:", "20"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 3", "Answer:", "30"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 4", "Answer:", "40"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 5", "Answer:", "50"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 6", "Answer:", "60"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 7", "Answer:", "70"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 8", "Answer:", "80"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 9", "Answer:", "90"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 10", "Answer:", "100"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 11", "Answer:", "110"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "10 X 12", "Answer:", "120"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 1", "Answer:", "11"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 2", "Answer:", "22"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 3", "Answer:", "33"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 4", "Answer:", "44"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 5", "Answer:", "55"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 6", "Answer:", "66"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 7", "Answer:", "77"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 8", "Answer:", "88"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 9", "Answer:", "99"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 10", "Answer:", "110"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 11", "Answer:", "121"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "11 X 12", "Answer:", "132"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 1", "Answer:", "12"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 2", "Answer:", "24"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 3", "Answer:", "36"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 4", "Answer:", "48"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 5", "Answer:", "60"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 6", "Answer:", "72"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 7", "Answer:", "84"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 8", "Answer:", "96"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 9", "Answer:", "108"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 10", "Answer:", "120"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 11", "Answer:", "132"),
                cardFactory.create("Question:", "12 X 12", "Answer:", "144")
            ]
        }
    }

})();
